{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Which of the terms listed below refers to the process of creating and maintaining computer applications?",
      "options": ["RAD", "SDLC", "OOP", "SaaS"],
      "correct_answers": ["SDLC"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following terms is used to describe all aspects of software development?",
      "options": ["PLC", "SDLC", "QA", "SDLM"],
      "correct_answers": ["SDLC"]
    },
    {
      "question": "A new-user setup checklist includes all the activities that enable a new hire to become productive... An end-user termination checklist deals with all the actions that should take place during the offboarding process. True or False?",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "correct_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the terms listed below best describes GDPR as an act of law?",
      "options": ["Regulatory", "Local", "Industry-specific", "Global"],
      "correct_answers": ["Regulatory"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following terms refers to an industry-specific regulation?",
      "options": ["RFC", "ISO", "PCI DSS", "GDPR"],
      "correct_answers": ["PCI DSS"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to an organization that develops a wide range of standards on a global level?",
      "options": ["IEEE", "ANSI", "ISO", "NIST"],
      "correct_answers": ["ISO"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which decision-making authorities assume responsibility for strategic direction and governance oversight at the highest level of an organization?",
      "options": ["Stakeholders", "Boards", "Committees", "Government entities"],
      "correct_answers": ["Boards"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following answers refers to a general term used to describe a specialized group within an organization focusing on specific tasks or areas of responsibility?",
      "options": ["Council", "Advisory board", "Committee", "Task force"],
      "correct_answers": ["Committee"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to public sector organizations that set and enforce laws and regulations at local, regional, or national levels?",
      "options": ["Government entities", "Trade associations", "Statutory bodies", "Regulatory agencies"],
      "correct_answers": ["Government entities"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following terms describes individuals or entities with overall accountability and authority over the data or system?",
      "options": ["Custodians", "Owners", "Processors", "Controllers"],
      "correct_answers": ["Owners"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to organizations or individuals responsible for ensuring compliance with data protection laws?",
      "options": ["Controllers", "Stewards", "Owners", "Processors"],
      "correct_answers": ["Controllers"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following answers refers to entities that act on behalf of the data controller to perform specific data-related tasks?",
      "options": ["Stewards", "Owners", "Processors", "Controllers"],
      "correct_answers": ["Processors"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refer(s) to individuals responsible for the day-to-day management, storage, and protection of data? (Select all that apply)",
      "options": ["Processors", "Controllers", "Stewards", "Owners", "Custodians"],
      "correct_answers": ["Stewards", "Custodians"]
    },
    {
      "question": "The process of determining potential risks that could affect an organization's ability to achieve its objectives is called:",
      "options": ["Risk assessment", "Risk identification", "Risk analysis", "Risk management"],
      "correct_answers": ["Risk identification"]
    },
    {
      "question": "The process of evaluating discovered risks to understand their potential impact and likelihood is referred to as:",
      "options": ["Risk analysis", "Risk assessment", "Risk identification", "Risk management"],
      "correct_answers": ["Risk assessment"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following answers refers to a risk assessment method based on need, typically conducted in response to specific events or changes?",
      "options": ["Ad hoc", "Recurring", "One-time", "Continuous"],
      "correct_answers": ["Ad hoc"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to an example of recurring risk assessment?",
      "options": ["Real-time monitoring of network security threats", "Assessing risk after a major change or breach", "Quarterly or annual risk assessments", "Risk assessment for a new product launch"],
      "correct_answers": ["Quarterly or annual risk assessments"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following answers refers to a risk assessment conducted for a specific purpose or project, without plans for regular reassessment?",
      "options": ["One-time", "Recurring", "Ad hoc", "Continuous"],
      "correct_answers": ["One-time"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to an example of continuous risk assessment?",
      "options": ["Quarterly or annual assessments", "Risk assessment for a new product launch", "Assessing risk after a major change or breach", "Real-time monitoring of network security threats"],
      "correct_answers": ["Real-time monitoring of network security threats"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Assessment of risk probability and its impact based on subjective judgment falls into the category of:",
      "options": ["Risk acceptance", "Quantitative risk assessment", "Risk tolerance", "Qualitative risk assessment"],
      "correct_answers": ["Qualitative risk assessment"]
    },
    {
      "question": "A calculation of SLE is an example of:",
      "options": ["Quantitative risk assessment", "Ad hoc risk assessment", "Qualitative risk assessment", "Recurring risk assessment"],
      "correct_answers": ["Quantitative risk assessment"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following terms is used to describe the predicted loss of value to an asset based on a single security incident?",
      "options": ["SLE", "ARO", "ALE", "SLA"],
      "correct_answers": ["SLE"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the acronyms listed below refers to a risk assessment formula defining probable financial loss due to a risk over a one-year period?",
      "options": ["ARO", "SLE", "ALE", "SLA"],
      "correct_answers": ["ALE"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following answers refers to the correct formula for calculating probable financial loss due to a risk over a one-year period?",
      "options": ["SLE = AV × EF", "ALE = ARO × SLE", "SLE = ALE × AV", "ALE = AV × EF"],
      "correct_answers": ["ALE = ARO × SLE"]
    },
    {
      "question": "In quantitative risk assessment, this term is used for estimating the likelihood of occurrence of a future threat.",
      "options": ["ALE", "SLA", "ARO", "SLE"],
      "correct_answers": ["ARO"]
    }
  ]
}